Guide to the Duke University Press Records, 1812-2019 UA.07.08.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Marketing Files, 1994-2015; 10
  - General Marketing Files, 11.1
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Wortham, Erica; Indigenous Media in Mexico, 2007-2012 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Wortham Original Review Slip (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Wortham ADs (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Wortham Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Wortham Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Wortham Publicity, 2013-2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Wortham: Indigenous Media in Mexico (F13), 2012-2013 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Wentzell, Emily; Maturing Machos, 2010-2012 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Wentzell Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Wentzell Publicity, 2013-2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Wentzell Original Review Slip (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Wentzell Copy & Blurbs (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Wentzell ADs (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Villarejo, Amy; Ethereal Queer, 2008-2013 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Villarejo/ Publicity, 2013-2015 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Villarejo/ Reviews, 2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Villarejo/ Ads (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Villarejo/ Original Review Slip, 2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Villarejo/ Copy and Blurbs (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Vazquez; Instrumental Migrations, 2007-2012 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Vazquez Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Vazquez Original Review Slips (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Vazquez Cover Copy & Blurbs, 2012-2013 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Vazquez ADs (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Vazquez Publicity, 2013-2015 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Trinh, Minh-ha; The D-Passage, 2012-2013 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Trinh/ Publicity (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Trinh/ Reviews, 2013-2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Trinh/ Ads (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Trinh/ Original Review Slip (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Trinh/ Copy and Blurbs (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Tinsman, Heidi; Buying into the Regime, 2002-2013 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Tinsman/ Copy and Blurbs (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Tinsman/ Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Tinsman/ Ads (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Tinsman/ Original Review Slip, 2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Tinsman/ Copy and Blurbs, 2011-2012 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Tinsman / Publicity, 2013-2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Thompson; The Privatization of Hope, 2012-2013 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Thompson/ Publicity, 2013-2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Thompson/ Ads (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Thompson/ original review slip, 2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Thompson/ Reviews, 2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Thompson/ Copy and Blurbs (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Stephen, Lynn; Making Rights a Reality, 2008-2012 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Stephen Publicity, 2013-2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Stephen Original Review Slips (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Stephen Cover Copy & Blurbs (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Stephen ADs (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Stephen Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Smith, Shawn Michelle; At the Edge of Sight, 2011-2013 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Smith Publicity, 2013-2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Smith Cover Copy & Blurbs (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Smith Original Review Slip (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Smith Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Smith Ads (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Sharma, Sarah; In the Meantime, 2008-2013 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Sharma/ Publicity, 2013-2015 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Sharma/ Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Sharma Original Review Slip, 2014 (Box 63)
    - Fall 2013 Marketing Files: Sharma/ Copy and Blurbs (Box 63)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Fernando, Mayanthi; On the Muslim Question, 2012-2014 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Fernando Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Fernando Cover Copy and Blurbs, 2013-2014 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Fernando Original Review Slip (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Fernando ADs (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Fernando Review, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Naranch and Eley; German Col., 2010-2014 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Naranch Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Eley Original Review Slips (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Eley Ads (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Eley Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dumm, Thomas; My Father's House, 2012-2014 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dumm Original Review Slip (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dumm Ads (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dumm Reviews (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dumm Publicity (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dumm Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dillon, Elizabeth Maddock; New World Drama, 2006-2013 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dillon / Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dillon \ Reviews, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dillon \ Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dillon \ Original Review Slip, 2014-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dillon \ Copy and Blurbs, 2013-2014 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dean, Tim; Porn Archives, 2013 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dean Reviews, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dean Original Review Slips (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dean Publicity, 2014-2016 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dean Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Dean Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Creech, Jimmy; Adam's Gift, 2010-2014 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Creech Reviews, 2009-2014 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Creech Publicity, 2010-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Cover Copy and ok Creech phk F14 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Creech Cover Copy, 2011 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Creech Original Review Slips, 2011 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Creech Ads, 2011-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Creech, 2011 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Cervenak, Sarah; Wandering: Between Performance and Philosophy, 2011-2013 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Cervenak Original Review Slip (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Cervenak Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Cervenak Cover Copy & Blurbs (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Cervenak ADs, 2014-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Cervenak Reviews, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Callison, Candis; How Climate Change Comes to Matter, 2012-2014 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Callison Publicity, 2014-2016 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Callison Ads (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Callison Reviews, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Callison Original Review Slip (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Callison Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Burton, Antoinette; Ten Books That Changed the British Empire, 2011-2014 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Burton Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Burton Copy and Blurbs (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Burton Orig. Review Slip (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Burton Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Behar, Ruth; Traveling Heavy (paperback f14), 2012-2013 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Behar Copy and Blurbs (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Behar Reviews (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Behar Ads (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Interior Pages (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Barnes, Jessica; Cultivating the Nile, 2012-2013 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Barnes Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Barnes Original Review Slip (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Barnes Reviews, 2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Barnes Cover Copy & Blurbs (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Barnes ADs, 2014-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Anker, Elisabeth; Orgies of Feeling, 2011-2014 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Anker Publicity, 2014-2016 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Anker Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Anker Original Review Slip (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Anker Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Anker Copy & Blurbs, 2013-2014 (Box 64)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Drinot & Knight; The Great Depression in the Americas, 2012-2013 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Drinot and Knight Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Drinot and Knight Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Drinot and Knight Original Review Slips (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Drinot and Knight Reviews, 2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Drinot and Knight Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Kirksey, Eben; The Multi Species Salon, 2012-2014 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Kirksey Publicity, 2014-2016 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Kirksey Original Review Slip (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Kirksey Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Kirksey Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Kirksey Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: James, CLR; Life of Captain Cipriani, 2013-2014 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: James Publicity, 2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: James Original Review Slip (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: James ADs, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: James Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: James Cover Copy & Blurbs (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Woolford, Andrew; Colonial Genocide in Indigenous North America, 2013-2014 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Woolford Ads (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Woolford Copy and Blurbs (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Woolford Orig. Review Slip (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Woolford Publicity, 2014-2016 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Woolford Reviews, 2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Halpern, Orit; The Eye of Time, 2010-2014 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Halpern Ads (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Halpern Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Halpern Publicity, 2015-2016 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Halpern Original Review Slip, 2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Gutierrez Aguilar; Rhythms of the Pachakuti, 2011-2014 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Gutierrez-Aguilar: Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Gutierrez-Aguilar: Orig. Review Slip (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Gutierrez-Aguilar: Copy and Blurbs, 2012-2014 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Gutierrez-Aguilar: Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Gutierrez-Aguilar: Reviews, 2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Guilbault, Jocelyne: My Laber of Love, 2013 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Guilbault Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Guilbault Reviews, 2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Guilbault Cover Copy and Blurbs, 2013-2014 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Guilbault Ads, 2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Green, Renee; Other Planes of There: Selected Writings, 2011-2014 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Green Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Green Original Review Slip (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Green Reviews, 2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Green Publicity (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Green Ads (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Gordillo, Gaston R; Rubble, 2009-2013 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Gordillo Publicity, 2014-2016 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Gordillo Copy and Blurbs (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Gordillo Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Gordillo Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Goodyear-Ka'opua, et al. Ea: Hawaiian Mvmts, 2012-2013 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Goodyear-Ka'opua: Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Goodyear-Ka'opua: Copy and Blurbs (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Goodyear-Ka'opua: Orig. Review Slip (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Goodyear-Ka'opua Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Goodyear-Ka'opua Ads (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Goldstein, Alyosha, ed.; Formations of United States Colonialism, 2013-2014 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Goldstein Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Goldstein Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Goldstein Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Goldstein Reviews, 2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Goldstein Original Review Slip (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Freeman, Carla; Enterprising Selves, 2011-2014 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Freeman Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Freeman Copy and Blurbs (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Freeman Orig. Review Slip, 2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Freeman Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Findlay, Eileen; We Are Left Without a Father Here, 2013-2014 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Findlay Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Findlay Copy and Blurbs (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Findlay Orig. Review Slip, 2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Findlay Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Findlay Reviews, 2015 (Box 65)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Nguyen, Hoang Tan; A View from the Bottom, 2010-2013 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Nguyen Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Nguyen Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Nguyen Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Nguyen Copy & Blurbs (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Nguyen Original Review Slip (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Miller-Young, Mireille; Brown Sugar: Black Women in Pornography, 2008-2014 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Miller-Young Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Miller-Young Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Miller-Young Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Miller-Young Reviews, 2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Miller-Young Original Review Slips (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Muniz de Albuquerque; Invention of Brazilian NE, 2013-2014 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Muniz de Albuquerque Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Muniz de Albuquerque Reviews, 2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Muniz du Albuquerque Original Review Slips (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Muniz du Albuquerque Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Muniz du Albuquerque Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: McGinley, Paige; The Scenic South: Staging Delta Blues from Tent Shows to Tourism, 2011-2013 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: McGinley Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: McGinley Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: McGinley Original Review Slip (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: McGinley Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: McGinley Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Massumi, Brian; What Animals Teach Us About Politics, 2013-2014 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Massumi Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Massumi Reviews, 2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Massumi Original Review Slip (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Massumi Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Massumi Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Masco, Joseph; Theater of Operations, 2012-2013 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Masco Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Masco Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Masco Reviews, 2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Masco Original Review Slip (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Masco Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Madera, Judith; Black Atlas, 2013-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Madera Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Madera Copy and Blurbs (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Madera Orig. Review Slips, 2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Madera Publicity, 2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Li, Tania Murray; Land's End: Wealth and Poverty in an Indonesian Frontier, 2012-2013 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Li Publicity, 2014-2016 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Li Ads (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Li Copy & Blurbs (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Li Original Review Slip (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Legg, Stephen; Scales of Prostitution, 2012-2014 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Legg, Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Legg Reviews, 2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Legg Original Review Slip (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Legg Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Legg Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Lawrence; A Rock Garden in the South, 2005-2014 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Lawrence, Armstrong, Wilson Reviews, 2007-2008 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Lawrence, Original Review Slip, 2006-2007 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Lawrence, Publicity, 2005-2007 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Lawrence \ Lindie Wilson, 2007 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Lawrence, Beautiful cover (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Lawrence, Armstrong, and Wilson Copy and Blurbs, 2006 (Box 66)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Stephens, Michelle; Skin Acts, 2010-2013 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Stephens Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Stephens Original Review Slip (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Stephens Cover Copy & Blurbs, 2013-2014 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Stephens ADs, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Stephens Reviews, 2012-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Smith, Tyson; Fighting for Recognition, 2010-2013 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Smith Publicity, 2014-2016 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Smith Reviews, 2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Smith Cover Copy & Blurbs, 2013-2014 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Smith ADs, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Sanders, James; The Vanguard of the Atlantic World, 2013-2014 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Sanders Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Sanders Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Sanders Original Review Slip (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Sanders Reviews, 2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Sanders Publicity (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Schechter, Kate; Illusions of a Future, 2011-2013 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Schechter Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Schechter Reviews, 2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Schechter Cover Copy & Blurbs (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Schechter ADs, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Shah, Svati; "Street Corner Secrets", 2008-2014 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Shah Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Shah Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Shah Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Shah Copy & Blurbs (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Siegel, Greg; Forensic Media & Culture, 2012-2014 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Siegel Ads (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Siegel Copy and Blurbs (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Siegel Original Review Slip (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Siegel Publicity (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Siegel Reviews, 2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Rosenberg, Emily; Body/Nation, 2012-2013 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Rosenberg: Reviews, 2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Rosenberg: Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Rosenberg: Copy and Blurbs (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Rosenberg: Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Rao, Vyjayanthi; Speculation, Now, 2013-2014 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Rao et al. Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Rao et al. Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Rao et al. Original Review Slips, 2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Rao et al. Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Ramberg, Lucinda; Given to the Goddess, 2011-2013 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Ramberg Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Ramberg Reviews, 2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Ramberg Original Review Slip (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Ramberg Ads, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Ramberg Cover Copy and Blurbs (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Quayson, Ato; Oxford St.,Accra, 2012-2014 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Quayson Publicity, 2014-2016 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Quayson Original Review Slip (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Quayson Cover Copy & Blurbs (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: quayson Reviews, 2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: quayson ADs, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Peterson, Kristin; Speculative Markets, 2013 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Peterson Publicity, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Peterson Reviews, 2014-2015 (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Peterson Original Review Slip (Box 67)
    - Fall 2014 Marketing Files: Peterson ADs (Box 67)